[{"question":"which object is bigger?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The bamboo cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"What is the material of the medium cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Leather"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Dirt"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Is the medium bamboo cube heavier than the medium concrete cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium leather cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium bamboo cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium leather cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium leather cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium concrete cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the medium concrete cube travel to quadrant \u2160?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2162?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the small porcelain cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the small porcelain cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium leather cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium leather cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small porcelain cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The medium leather cube and the medium concrete cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium leather cube and the medium bamboo cube"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium leather cube and the medium concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium leather cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The medium concrete cube and the medium bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube and the small porcelain cube"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Will the medium leather cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0}]